Discover a world of wishes and wonder
Jingle Jangle: A Christmas Journey is a family, fantasy,
music film directed by David E. Talbert.
An imaginary world comes to life in a holiday tale of an eccentric toymaker, his adventurous
granddaughter, and a magical invention that has the power to change their lives forever.
Jeronicus Jangle, played by Forest Whitaker.
Gustafson, played by Keegan-Michael Key.
Mr. Delacroix, played by Hugh Bonneville.
Jessica, played by Anika Noni Rose.
Journey, played by Madalen Mills.
Grandmother Journey, played by Phylicia Rashād.
Jingle Jangle: A Christmas Journey is a 2020 American Christmas
musical fantasy film written and directed by David E.
Choreographed by Ashley Wallen, it stars Forest Whitaker, Keegan-Michael Key, Hugh Bonneville, Anika
Noni Rose, Phylicia Rashad, Lisa Davina Phillip, Ricky Martin, and Madalen Mills.
The film, which was originally planned as a stage production, received 10 nominations at the 52nd NAACP Image Awards, which
was the overall most to be held by a motion picture tied with Black Panther and The Best Man in previous years.
This record was succeeded by The Color Purple who surpassed
the number of nominations four years later.
The film was released on Netflix on November 13, 2020.
The film explores themes of inventor, holiday, invention, musical, steampunk.